James F. McNulty Papers, 1925-2002
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Subgroup 1: Political Activity, 1957 – 1985
  - Series 2: Arizona State Legislature, 1968 – 1976
    - Arizona State Senate—31st legislature (II), 1973-1974—Correspondence, October 1974 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Arizona State Senate—31st legislature (II), 1973-1974—Correspondence, November 1974 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Arizona State Senate—31st legislature (II), 1973-1974—Correspondence, December 1974 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Arizona State Senate—31st legislature (II), 1973-1974—Correspondence, January 1975 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Arizona State Senate—31st legislature (II), 1973-1974—Correspondence, July-September 1975 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Arizona State Senate—31st legislature (I), 1973-1974—Senate Land Fraud Committee, March 1973 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Arizona State Senate—31st legislature (II), 1973-1974—Senate Land Fraud Committee, June-July 1974 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Arizona State Senate—31st legislature (II), 1973-1974—Senate Land Fraud Committee, August 1974 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Arizona State Senate—31st legislature (II), 1973-1974—Senate Land Fraud Committee, September-December 1974 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Arizona State Senate—31st legislature 1973-1974—Committee to reorganize lower courts—Research— (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Arizona State Senate—31st legislature 1973-1974—Committee to reorganize lower courts—Reports— (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Arizona State Senate—31st legislature 1973-1974—Committee to reorganize lower courts—Reports—, April 1973 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Arizona State Senate—31st legislature (II), 1973-1974—Correspondence—Senate Bill 1162 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Arizona State Senate—Eagleton’s Legislative Center, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Arizona State Senate—Press release, No Date (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Arizona State Senate—Voting record of Senator James F. McNulty, 1969-1974 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Arizona State Senate—33rd legislative (I), 1977-1978—Commission on salaries for elective state officers, February-May 1977 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Arizona State Senate—33rd legislative (I), 1977-1978—Commission on salaries for elective state officers, June 1977 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Arizona State Senate—33rd legislative (I), 1977-1978—Commission on salaries for elective state officers, July-August 1977 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Arizona State Senate—33rd legislative (I), 1977-1978—Commission on salaries for elective state officers, September 1977 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Arizona State Senate—33rd legislative (I), 1977-1978—Commission on salaries for elective state officers, November 1977 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Arizona State Senate—33rd legislative (I), 1977-1978—Commission on salaries for elective state officers, December 1977 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Arizona State Senate—33rd legislative (II), 1977-1978—Commission on salaries for elective state officers, January-June 1978 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Arizona State Senate—33rd legislative (II), 1977-1978—Commission on salaries for elective state officers—Arizona state reports (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Series 3: Campaign Files, 1968 - 1985
    - Subseries 1: Arizona State Senate, 1968 - 1974
      - Campaign Files—Arizona State Senate, September 1968 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Campaign Files—Arizona State Senate, July-September 1970 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Campaign Files—Arizona State Senate, October-December 1970 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Subseries 2 U.S. House of Representatives, 1974 – 1985
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, January 1975 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, February 1975 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, March-April 1975 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, May-July 1975 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, August-September 1975 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, October 1975 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, November-December 1975 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, January 1976 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, February 1976 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, March 1976 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, March 1976 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, April 1976 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, May 1976 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, June-September 1976 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence—Federal Elections Commission, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence—Federal Elections Commission, January-October 1975 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence—Federal Elections Commission, November-December 1975 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence—Federal Elections Commission, January 1976 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence—Federal Elections Commission, February-March 1976 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence—Federal Elections Commission, April 1976 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence—Federal Elections Commission, May-June 1976 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence—Federal Elections Commission, July-October 1976 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Federal Elections Commission, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Federal Elections Commission, 1976-1976 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Position papers, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Precinct committee, 1972-1975 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Press releases, July 1975-May 1976 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Speeches, 1974, No Date (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Demographic analysis 5th congressional district, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Endorsements, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Fundraising invitations, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Gary Hart’s visit, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Press releases, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Promotional material, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Promotional material, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Speeches, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Stationary, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, December 9-10, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, December 13, 1982-February 22, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, February 24-August 29, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, August 30-December 12, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 13)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, December 19, 1983-January 3, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, January 4-April 23, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, April 24-August 17, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, August 20-September 4, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, September 8-December 18, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, December 19-26, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, January 2-9, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, January 9-15, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, January 17-February 9, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, No Date (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Election, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Ephemera, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—IMF and Copper, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Invitation form, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Kolbe, Jim, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Promotional material, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Promotional material—Jim Kolbe, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Questionnaire, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Reports, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Reports, 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Republican news clippings, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 12)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Response to critique of voting record, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Speeches, February-June 1983 (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Speeches, July-September 1983 (Box 19, Folder 15)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Speeches, January-August 1984 (Box 19, Folder 16)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Speeches, September-November 1984 (Box 19, Folder 17)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. House of Representatives—Speeches, No Date (Box 19, Folder 18)
      - Campaign Files—The Bisbee Papers, No Date (Box 96, Folder 10)
      - Campaign Files—Memos, correspondence, statistics, 1982-1983 (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - Subseries 3 U.S. Senate, 1979 – 1980
      - Campaign Files—U.S. Senate Race—Biography and Legislative History, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. Senate Race—Correspondence—Campaign Related, May 1979-December 1979 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. Senate Race—Correspondence—Campaign Related, January 1980 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. Senate Race—Correspondence—Campaign Related, February 1980 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. Senate Race—Correspondence—Campaign Related, March 1980 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. Senate Race—Correspondence—Campaign Related, April 1980 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. Senate race—Correspondence—Campaign Related, May 1980 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. Senate race—Correspondence—Campaign Related, June 1980 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. Senate Race—Correspondence—Campaign Related, July 1980 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. Senate Race—Correspondence—Campaign Related, August 1980–September 1980 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. Senate Race—Correspondence—Dennis Deconcini, May 3, 1979-August 15, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. Senate race—Correspondence—Personal, September 1979-October 1979 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - Campaign Files—U.S Senate Race—Correspondence—Personal, November 1979-December 1979 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - Campaign Files—U.S Senate Race—Correspondence—Personal, January 1980-February 1980 (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - Campaign Files—U.S Senate Race—Correspondence—Personal, March 1980-April 1980 (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. Senate Race—Correspondence—Personal, May 1980-August 1980 (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - Campaign Files—U.S Senate Race—Correspondence—Personal, September 2, 1980-September 17, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - Campaign Files—U.S Senate Race—Correspondence—Personal, September 18, 1980-September 30, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 9)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. Senate Race—Correspondence—Personal, October 1980-December 1981 (Box 21, Folder 10)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. Senate Race—Correspondence—Morris Udall, January 29,1979-August 28,1979 (Box 21, Folder 11)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. Senate Race—Correspondence, No Date (Box 21, Folder 12)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. Senate Race—Federal Election Commission, January 1976-September 1979 (Box 21, Folder 13)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. Senate Race—Federal Election Commission, 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 14)
      - Campaign Files—U.S Senate Race, 1979-1980—Ephemera (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. Senate Race—Newspapers articles and Reports, April 1978-May 1980 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. Senate Race—Nomination Papers, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. Senate Race—Photographs, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. Senate Race—Political Action Committees, August 1978-March 1980 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. Senate Race—Position Papers, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. Senate Race—Press Conferences, August 1980-September 1980 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. Senate Race—Press Releases, Speeches, and Statements, November 1979-June 1980 (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. Senate Race—Press Releases, Speeches, and Statements, July 1980-September 1980 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. Senate Race—Public Relations, April 1978-February 1979 (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. Senate Race—Research Organizations, 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 11)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. Senate Race—Senate Reports, April 1979-August 1980 (Box 22, Folder 12)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. Senate—Washington Trip, December 2-5, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 13)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. Senate, 1979-1980—Survey of Voter Attitudes in the State of Arizona—Tables TS3-Appendix, March 1980 (Box 22, Folder 14)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. Senate, 1979-1980—Survey of Voter Attitudes in the State of Arizona—Tables T1-t52, March 1980 (Box 22, Folder 15)
      - Campaign Files—U.S. Senate, 1979-1980—Survey of Voter Attitudes in the State of Arizona, March 1980 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Series 4 U.S. House of Representatives, 1982 – 1985
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Certificate of Election, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - U.S House of Representatives—Christmas Cards, No Date (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Congressional Record—Vol. 129 No. 4, No Date (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Congressional Record, No Date (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, January 5, 1983-January 15, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, January 16, 1983-January 24, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, January 25, 1983-January 31, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, February 1, 1983-February 9, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, February 10, 1983-February 22, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, February 23, 1983-February 28, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, March 1, 1983-March 9, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, March 10, 1983-March 19, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, March 20, 1983-March 31, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, April 1, 1983-April 7, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, April 8, 1983-April, 15, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, April 18, 1983-April 29, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, May 1, 1983-May 9, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, May 10, 1983-May 20, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, May 22, 1983-May 31, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, June 1, 1983-June 9, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, June 10, 1983-June 20, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, June 21, 1983-June 30, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, July 1, 1983-July13, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, July 14, 1983-July 22, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, July 25, 1983-July 29, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, August 1, 1983-August 8, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, August 9, 1983-August 24, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, August 25, 1983-August 31, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, September 1, 1983-September 12, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, September 13, 1983-September 15, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, September 16, 1983-September 31, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, October 3, 1983-October 11, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, October 12, 1983-October 19, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, October 20, 1983-October 31, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, November 1, 1983-November 7, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, November 8, 1983-November 10, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, November 11, 1983-November 16, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, November 17, 1983-November 30, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, December 1, 1983-December 8, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, December 9, 1983-December 19, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, December 20, 1983-December 29, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, nd. 1983 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, January 3, 1984-January 16, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, January 17, 1984-January 25, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, January 26, 1984-January 31,1984 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, February 1, 1984-February 14, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, February 15, 1984- February 21, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, February 22, 1984-February 29, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, March 1, 1984-March 13, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, March 14, 1984-March 22, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, March 23, 1984-March 30,1984 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, April 2, 1984-April 9, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, April, 10, 1984- April 20, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, March 23, 1984-March 30, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, May 1, 1984- May 9, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, May 10, 1984- May 21, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, May 22, 1984-May 31, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, June 1, 1984- June 13, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, June 14, 1984-June 21, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, June 22, 1984-June 29, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, July 2, 1984-July 20, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, July 23, 1983-July 31, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, August 1, 1984-August 10, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, August 13, 1984-August 31, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, September 4, 1984-September 17, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, September 18, 1984-September 28, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, October 1, 1984-October 4, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, October 5, 1984-October 11, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, October 17, 1984-October 30, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, November 1, 1984-November 9, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, November 13, 1984-November 15, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, November 16, 1984-November 19, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, November 20, 1984-November 27, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, November 28, 1984-November 30, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, December 1984 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Correspondence, No Date (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Defense articles, No Date (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Democratic Study Group—Record Votes—98th Congress—1st Session—part 1, No Date (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Democratic Study Group—Record Votes—98th Congress—1st Session—part 2, No Date (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Democratic Study Group—Record Votes—98th Congress—1st Session—part 3, No Date (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Democratic Study Group—Record Votes—98th Congress—2nd Session—part 1, No Date (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Democratic Study Group—Record Votes—98th Congress—2nd Session—part 2, No Date (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Democratic Study Group—Record Votes—98th Congress—2nd Session—part 3, No Date (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Directory, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Editorials, No Date (Box 29, Folder 2)